[Music]
[音乐]
okay hi everyone my name is Alex Buckley
好的，大家好，我叫Alex Buckley
I work in the Java platform group at
我在Java平台小组工作，
Oracle this is modular development with
Oracle这是模块化开发
JDK 9 thank you for coming
JDK 9谢谢您的光临
Jenny k-9 is fast approaching and
珍妮k-9快到了
there's a lot in it some of the features
其中有很多功能
are performance improvements such as
性能改进，例如
compact strings
紧凑的弦
some are tooling improvements like the
有些是工具方面的改进，例如
search box in Java doc has anyone seen
Java doc中的搜索框看到任何人
that by the way into the canine the
顺便说一下，
search box some it's pretty cool the J
搜索框有些酷J
shell tool does anyone tried that good
shell工具有人尝试过吗
yep
是的
and of course there are lots of updates
当然会有很多更新
to existing features such as support for
现有功能，例如对
Unicode 8 but the main feature and the
Unicode 8但主要功能和
one that's taken some years to come to
一个花了几年的时间
fruition is the module system the module
成果是模块系统模块
system is a big deal because it enables
系统很重要，因为它可以
modular development all the way down the
一直到模块化开发
module system is built into the Java
Java中内置了模块系统
language and the Java Virtual Machine
语言和Java虚拟机
so that the applications you write and
这样您编写的应用程序以及
the libraries you consume and even the
您消耗的库，甚至
JDK itself can all be developed and
JDK本身可以全部开发和
tested and packaged and deployed as
经过测试，打包和部署为
modules managed by the module system
由模块系统管理的模块
making everyone play by the same modular
让每个人都使用相同的模块
rules has great benefits for reliability
规则对可靠性有很大好处
maintainability and security as we'll
维护性和安全性
see in the rest of this talk so with the
在本讲的其余部分中请参见
theme of modules all the way down in
模块主题一直向下
mind this talk has three parts the first
请注意，本次演讲分为三个部分
part explains how modules are a
部分说明模块是如何
long-overdue building block in the
逾期未决的构建基块
structure of application code the second
应用程序代码结构第二
part is about how applications and the
部分是关于应用程序和
libraries data pendin can migrate to
Pendin可以迁移到的库数据
modules more broadly it's about how you
更广泛的模块是关于您
can mix modular code and on modular code
可以混合模块化代码和模块化代码
the third part is about the structure of
第三部分是关于
the modular JDK including some of the
模块化JDK，其中包括一些
compatibility issues that arise from it
由此产生的兼容性问题
so programming in the large modular
因此在大型模块化中进行编程
applications in object-oriented
面向对象的应用
programming the basic unit of reuse is
编程重用的基本单位是
traditionally the class programs or
传统上，班级课程或
classes Java has wonderful mechanisms
Java类具有出色的机制
for promoting reuse of a class
用于促进班级的重用
inheritance for reusing behavior
重用行为的继承
interfaces for reusing abstractions
重用抽象的接口
separate compilation dynamic linking and
单独的编译动态链接和
access control all the way down to the
访问控制一直到
level of individual fields and methods
各个领域和方法的水平
and we've had nested classes since 1997
自1997年以来我们就开始嵌套课程
so it should be possible for a single
所以应该有可能一个
top-level class to encapsulate a vast
顶级类来封装大量
amount of functionality with that in
具有的功能
mind I'm setting up a strawman here but
介意我在这里设置一个稻草人，但是
keep going with that in mind it seems
记住这一点，似乎
like an application could be a single
就像一个应用程序可能是一个
package containing a few very rich
包含一些非常丰富的包装
classes all sharing data via fields and
通过字段对所有共享数据进行分类
methods accessible within the package
包中可访问的方法
and where a handful of public classes
以及少数公共课程
form the entry points or the API of the
形成入口或API的API
application right not really
申请权不是真的
how many people work on a code base that
有多少人在一个代码库上工作
consists in your application of one
包含在您的应用程序中
package no hands right answer two
包没有手正确答案二
packages three packages five order of
套餐三套餐五顺序
ten packages in your codebase one we
您的代码库中有十个软件包
have a few on the order of 10 a 17 ok at
在10点到17点之间有一些
least minute right right right
至少一分钟右右右
everyone knows the minimum but who knows
每个人都知道最低限度，但谁知道
the maximum order of perhaps 50 packages
可能最多订购50个包裹
there's that there are some hands maybe
也许有一些手
some hands the are sort of shooting up
有些手在射击
just just your codes your short digital
只是您的代码您的短数字
code now the point is no one uses a
现在的代码是没有人使用
handful of packages anymore even the
很少的软件包，甚至
smallest microservice wouldn't be
最小的微服务不会
expected to fit into a single package
预计将适合单个包装
programs are packages multiple packages
程序是软件包多个软件包
not classes unfortunately the Java
不幸的是，没有类
language kind of gives up once your
语言放弃了一次
program is bigger than a package here's
程序比这里的包大
the hierarchy of accessibility in Java
Java中可访问性的层次结构
it's simple to understand easy to use
简单易懂易用
and strongly enforced at compile-time
并在编译时强力执行
and run-time but it has a big weakness
和运行时，但它有一个很大的缺点
your program is some dozens of packages
您的程序是几十个软件包
but the only way to share code between
但是在之间共享代码的唯一方法
packages is by making things public but
打包是通过将事物公开
then you're sharing with everyone it's
那么你就是与所有人分享
not surprising that packaged friendship
打包的友谊并不奇怪
in one form or another has been
以一种或另一种形式
requested many times over the years a
多年来要求多次
package is a fine way to organize
打包是组织的好方法
classes but most people wish there was a
课，但大多数人希望有一个
way to organize packages too now of
现在也可以组织软件包的方法
course you can put some packages in one
当然你可以把一些包放在一个
jar file and other packages in another
jar文件和其他包中的另一个
jar file and so on but that's after
jar文件等，但是之后
compilation it doesn't help you control
编译并不能帮助您控制
access from one package to another
从一个包装进入另一个包装
during development wouldn't you prefer
在开发过程中，您不喜欢
to group your packages in a logical
将您的包裹按逻辑分组
fashion when you're actually developing
当你真正发展时的时尚
them nodding heads perhaps yeah good
他们点头，也许是的，很好
thinking as to that yes there are some
想着，是的，有一些
nodding heads in the audience that
观众点头表示
brings me to modules in JDK 9 a module
带我进入JDK 9中的模块
in JDK 9 is a set of packages that make
JDK 9中的一组软件包
sense being grouped together this is the
感觉在一起，这是
classic software engineering principle
经典软件工程原理
of high cohesion some of the packages
高凝聚力的一些包装
are intended for use by code outside the
适用于外部的代码
module these are exported packages some
这些模块是一些导出包
of the packages are internal to the
套件的内部
module they can be used by code inside
模块可以被内部代码使用
the module but not by code outside these
模块，但不是通过这些之外的代码
are concealed packages now the word use
是隐藏的包装，现在使用一词
keeps coming up used by use by use by
不断使用
this code a module is the unit of reuse
此代码是模块的重用单位
it describes which of its packages of
它描述了它的哪个包装
external use and which are concealed
外用和隐藏
internal use a program built of modules
内部使用由模块构建的程序
will be more reliable than a program
比程序更可靠
built of a loose set of packages that
由一组松散的程序包构建而成
can access each other freely and that
可以互相自由访问
exposed to many AP is to the outside
暴露于许多AP的外部
world
世界
let's look at the Java base module this
让我们看一下Java基本模块
is the foundation in gdk9 of the Java
是Java gdk9的基础
rescue platform it it grouped the
它将救援平台分组
essential Java star and Java X dot star
必不可少的Java星和Java X点星
packages that most programs need it's
大多数程序需要的软件包
where java.lang object and Java IO file
其中java.lang对象和Java IO文件
and Java util list live it declared in a
和Java util列表将其声明为
file called module info Java this gives
这给出了名为模块信息Java的文件
the name of the module and its exported
模块的名称及其导出的
packages what does it mean to export the
打包导出的意思是
java.lang package it means that the
java.lang包意味着
public classes of java.lang are
java.lang的公共类是
accessible to code outside this module a
可访问此模块外部的代码
package that is not explicitly exported
没有明确导出的包
is concealed in the java base module in
隐藏在Java基本模块中
in red many comments on and some
红色，有很多评论，还有一些
packages are concealed their public
包对公众隐瞒
classes are not accessible from outside
不能从外部访问课程
the Java based module this is the first
基于Java的模块，这是第一个
goal of the module system strong
模块系统的目标很强
encapsulation a module isn't just a set
封装模块不仅仅是一组
of packages it's a set of exported
包，它是一组导出的
packages and conceals packages the
包装和隐藏包装
public classes of exported packages are
导出包的公共类是
accessible outside the module the public
公众可以在模块外部访问
classes of concealed packages are not
隐藏包的类别不是
accessible outside the module so the
可在模块外部访问，因此
hierarchy of accessibility is bigger in
可访问性的层次更大
jdk 9 than in jdk AIDS reading upwards
jdk 9比jdk AIDS中的阅读量更高
on the right you can arrange for public
在右边你可以安排公开
classes to be accessible only within
类只能在内部访问
their module or accessible within their
他们的模块或在他们的内部可以访问
module and to other specific modules or
模块和其他特定模块，或
accessible to everyone so to be clear in
每个人都可以访问，以便在
jeddah key 9 if you're looking at public
吉达钥匙9如果您正在公开场合
on the class declaration it no longer
在类声明上不再
means that everyone can access the class
意味着每个人都可以访问课程
access depends on whether the class is
访问权限取决于该类是否为
module export the class's package since
从模块导出类的包，因为
Java base is a module let's reuse it
Java base是一个模块，让我们重复使用它
with a module of our own
有我们自己的模块
here's the simplest possible program in
这是最简单的程序
one package komm example hello let's
一包komm示例你好，让我们
declare a module to put that package in
声明一个模块以将该包放入
hello world there's a module in photo
你好，世界上有一个模块
Java file and for sake of argument the
Java文件，为了便于讨论
module will export the calm example
模块将导出平静示例
Hello package with the exports directive
你好包与exports指令
you're probably wondering how the hello
你可能想知道你好
world module knows that it has a package
世界模块知道它有一个包装
called comm example hello after all
毕竟叫comm example hello
nothing in the package seems to point to
包装中似乎没有任何东西指向
the module it's up to the tooling to
该模块取决于工具
decide during development which module
在开发期间决定哪个模块
each package belongs to in practice your
每个包实际上都属于您
IDE will take care of it you'll create a
IDE会照顾您的，您将创建一个
modular job or application be asked the
要求模块化作业或应用
name of the module then every package
然后是每个包装的模块名称
you create will just be passed to that
您创建的将被传递给
module let's know they're there it just
模块让我们知道他们在那里
happens if you run Java C by hands then
如果您手动运行Java C，则会发生
Java C figures out which module each
Java C找出每个模块
package is in that's why the module info
包就是这就是为什么模块信息
Java file is at the same level in SRC as
Java文件在SRC中的级别与
the common directory containing the
包含
package the benefit of relying on
包依赖的好处
tooling is that it's really easy to
工具是，它真的很容易
place an existing package in a module
将现有包放在模块中
and immediately give that package the
然后立即给那个包裹
benefit of strong encapsulation
强封装的好处
we don't want each and every class to
我们不想每个班级都去
have to opt in to strongly encapsulation
必须选择强力封装
by declaring the module it belongs to
通过声明它属于的模块
that would invite errors such as classes
会引起诸如类的错误
in the same package attempting to join
在同一包中尝试加入
different modules that's a big no-no for
不同的模块非常重要
reasons I'll mention later one more
我稍后再提及的原因
thing the say hello class in the package
东西在包装里打个招呼类
imports the java.lang package where is
导入java.lang包，其中
that package imported from now you might
从现在开始导入的软件包
say Alex the answer is obviously Java
说亚历克斯，答案显然是Java
base because you told me a minute ago
基地，因为你在一分钟前告诉我
the Java based exports the java.lang
基于Java的导出java.lang
package I had a slide that showed it and
包中有一张幻灯片显示了
your rights but how does the compiler
您的权利，但编译器如何
know that in general when you import a
知道一般情况下，当您导入
package should the compiler search the
包，编译器应搜索
file system looking for modules which
文件系统中寻找哪些模块
export to imported package
出口到进口包装
what if multiple modules export the
如果多个模块导出
imported package obviously java.lang is
导入的包显然java.lang是
a special case but in general how would
特殊情况，但总的来说
a compiler know which module exports a
编译器知道哪个模块导出一个
package if we intend to reuse the Java
包，如果我们打算重用Java
based module we should document that
基于模块，我们应该证明
fact actually since we're writing a
实际上，因为我们正在写一个
module ourselves we must document that
我们必须自己做模块
fact this is the second goal of the
事实上，这是
module system reliable dependencies a
模块系统可靠的依赖关系
module isn't just a set of packages it's
模块不仅仅是一组软件包
a set of packages that depend on the
一组取决于
packages exported by other modules so
包由其他模块导出，因此
the HelloWorld module specifies that it
HelloWorld模块指定它
reuses the Java based module with a
将基于Java的模块与
requires directive in its module in
在其模块中的require指令
photo Java
图片Java
this means that code in the HelloWorld
这意味着HelloWorld中的代码
module can import any of the packages
模块可以导入任何软件包
exported by Java base
由Java库导出
what happens if code in hello world
如果代码在hello world中会发生什么
tries to import any of the packages
尝试导入任何软件包
conceals by Java base such as and
由Java基础隐藏，例如和
there's one in red some security
有一个红色的一些安全
provider here's a real example of some
提供者是一些例子
code that does that GlassFish 4.1 it
完成GlassFish 4.1的代码
doesn't run on jdk 9 because the VM
无法在jdk 9上运行，因为VM
throws an illegal access error the error
抛出非法访问错误
message is a class concern enterprise
留言是一个班级关注企业
security provide a policy wrapper in
安全提供策略包装
module unnamed module don't worry
模块未命名模块不用担心
bailout cannot access class some
纾困无法访问某些课程
security provide a policy file in module
安全性在模块中提供策略文件
Java base now a glance at the open JDK
Java基础现在可以看一下开放的JDK
repository shows us that the policy file
存储库向我们显示该策略文件
class is declared public in the sun
该课程在阳光下宣布为公共
security provider package but because
安全提供程序包，但是因为
that package is not exported by java
该包不是由java导出的
base policy file is only accessible from
基本策略文件只能从以下位置访问
code in java base itself so to be clear
Java基础本身中的代码，因此要清楚
in jetty k9 the GlassFish code cannot
在码头k9中，GlassFish代码无法
access the public policy file class at
访问位于的公共策略文件类
compile time or runtime it's exactly
编译时间或运行时
like trying to access a package private
就像尝试访问私有包一样
class from outside the package Java C
包Java C外部的类
gives an error the VM throws in a legal
给出虚拟机抛出合法错误
access error GlassFish will need to find
访问错误GlassFish将需要查找
a supported API not a Sun dot star API
受支持的API，而不是Sun dot star API
to do its work
做好工作
I'd like to return to the module Inferno
我想回到Inferno模块
Java file that declares the hello world
宣告世界的Java档案
module it's really important to
模块真的很重要
understand that a module exports
了解模块导出
packages but it requires modules the
包，但需要模块
reason is due to an old software
原因是由于旧软件
engineering principle the unit of reuse
工程原理重用单位
is the unit of release the principle is
是释放单位，原理是
about separation of concerns you reuse
关于重用关注点分离的问题
someone's code not by copy pasting it
某人的代码，而不是复制粘贴
into your own source tree but by
到您自己的源代码树中，但是
depending in some way on the black box
在某种程度上取决于黑匣子
artifact released by someone else now in
现在由其他人释放的工件
the Java ecosystem there's no question
Java生态系统毫无疑问
that the unit of release is a jar file
释放单元是一个jar文件
that doesn't change with modules a jar
罐子的模块不会改变
file as HelloWorld aa jar that's what
文件作为HelloWorld一个jar就是
you built today simply carries the
您今天建造的只是带有
module info dot class file that a
模块信息点类文件
compiler produced from module in photo
由照片中的模块生成的编译器
Java alongside an ordinary class files
Java以及普通的类文件
like say hello we call this a modular
像打个招呼，我们称之为模块化
jar so when someone releases a modular
罐子，所以当有人释放模块化
jar for their module its reused by
将其模块重用
someone else writing requires hello
别人写作需要打招呼
world in their own module in futur Java
Java自己的模块中的世界
the re user benefits from an explicit
重新使用者受益于明确的
coherent API consisting of precisely the
相干的API恰好由
exported packages the releaser benefits
导出的软件包释放者的好处
from strong encapsulation of conceals
遮盖物的强力封装
packages inside the module which
包里面的模块
underpin the API even if there's high
即使存在很高的API
coupling inside a module there's loose
模块内部耦合松动
coupling between modules that's another
模块之间的耦合是另一个
good software engineering principle so
好的软件工程原理
as the release are you're exporting
作为您要导出的版本
packages but as the reuse err you're
包，但是作为重用错误，
you're consuming modules ok so you want
您正在使用模块，所以您想要
to require Java base from your
需要您的Java基础
HelloWorld module when you say requires
您说需要的HelloWorld模块
Java base in module in photo Java where
照片Java模块中的Java基础，其中
does the compiler physically look for it
编译器在物理上寻找它吗
and if you've built the modular jar file
如果您已经构建了模块化jar文件
for HelloWorld jar containing module in
包含模块的HelloWorld jar
photo class where do you physically put
照相课你身体放在哪里
that jar
那罐子
well JDK 9 looks for modules in the
JDK 9会在
system image and on the module path the
系统映像和模块路径上的
system image is in the JDK installation
系统映像在JDK安装中
directory
目录
it contains Java base and a few dozen
它包含Java基础和几十个
core JDK modules the module path is set
核心JDK模块的模块路径已设置
on the command line like the class path
在命令行上，例如类路径
except that the module path points to
除了模块路径指向
directories containing modular jars
包含模块化jar的目录
rather than the jars themselves which is
而不是罐子本身
pretty convenient it makes the the
非常方便，它使
module pastor says looking at the libs
牧师说看库
and there's a whole bunch of there are
还有一大堆
hundreds of modular jars perhaps in each
每个可能有数百个模块化罐
directory now the key point about
目录现在关于
modules requiring each other is that the
彼此需要的模块是
module system can check the requirements
模块系统可以检查要求
and validate that a modular application
并验证模块化应用程序
is sound once the compiler or runtime
编译器或运行时发出声音
has found the initial hello world module
找到了最初的hello world模块
my not benign assembles in the system
我的非良性组装系统
image or on the module path it performs
映像或它执行的模块路径
a process called resolution resolution
一个称为分辨率解析的过程
means inspecting it requires directives
意味着检查它需要指令
and finding those required modules in
并在其中找到那些必需的模块
the system image or on the module path
系统映像或模块路径上
and then recursively resolving them
然后递归地解决它们
we're building a graph whose nodes are
我们正在建立一个节点为
modules and whose edges are the requires
模块及其边缘是必需的
relation and to be clear in JDK 9 we do
关系，并且要在JDK 9中明确说明
this at compile-time and run-time if
如果在编译时和运行时
resolutions succeed you get three
决议成功你得到三个
guarantees first every module that is
首先保证每个模块
required is available okay pretty
必需的，可以的，很好
obvious but a big improvement over the
明显，但比
class path where you don't discover
您找不到的课程路径
missing jars until later seconds modules
缺少罐子，直到稍后的模块
don't depend on each other in a cycle
不在一个周期内互相依赖
cyclic dependencies are a design smell
循环依赖性是一种设计气味
and we're taking the opportunity to
我们正借此机会
prohibit them in modules from day one of
从第一天开始禁止他们进入模块
JDK 9 now some of you are thinking Alex
JDK 9现在有些人在想Alex
this is just dependency management
这只是依赖管理
haven't you heard of maven who is
你没有听说过行家
thinking that you're definitely not
以为你绝对不是
but definitely not thinking of an
但绝对不会想到
elephant you're not thinking sure
大象，你不确定
cyclic dependences are well yeah now let
周期性依赖性很好，现在让
me say maven only works at compile time
我说Maven仅在编译时有效
and this resolution process works at
此解决过程适用于
runtime as well but more importantly let
运行时也一样，但更重要的是让
me come to resolutions third guarantee
我来决议第三个保证
if coding one module
如果编码一个模块
imports a package then that package is
导入一个包，然后该包是
exported from exactly one other module
从另一个模块导出
now this guarantee obviously relies on
现在，这种保证显然取决于
exports as well as requires so you won't
出口以及需求，所以您不会
find it in maven it means there are no
在Maven中找到它意味着没有
splits packages which is what happens
拆分包，这是怎么回事
when two jars on the classpath contained
当类路径上的两个罐子包含
the same package and you load some
相同的包装，您会加载一些
classes in the package from one jar and
从一个罐子包装中的类和
other classes in the package from the
包中的其他类
other jar split packages are a huge
其他罐子拆分包装是巨大的
failing of the class path mechanism
类路径机制的失败
because they lead to incredibly
因为它们导致了难以置信的
difficult to debug scenarios because of
由于以下原因很难调试方案
resolution they are completely
分辨率他们是完全
impossible in a modular application
在模块化应用中是不可能的
which is great for long term maintenance
这对于长期维护非常有用
and this is really what we mean by
这就是我们的意思
reliable dependencies the dependencies
可靠的依赖关系
in a graph of modules are reliable when
在模块图中是可靠的
each module can access only one version
每个模块只能访问一个版本
of a package at a time
一次打包
and the third guarantee is a big deal
第三个保证很重要
for performance too because we know
也是为了表现，因为我们知道
which module exports which package
哪个模块导出哪个包
there's no need to scan every module in
无需扫描其中的每个模块
the system image and on the module path
系统映像和模块路径上
when trying to load a class contrast
尝试加载类对比时
that with how you load classes from the
与如何从
class path this is the class path some
上课路径这是上课路径
of you Mason's before the class path
你们梅森在上课之前
from Hadoop the compiler or runtime has
从Hadoop编译器或运行时
to do a linear search through 110 jars
通过110个罐子进行线性搜索
whenever a new class is needed now of
现在每当需要一门新课时
course the implementation can speed
当然实施可以加快
things up by caching the classes it
通过缓存类来解决问题
found when it wasn't looking for them
在找不到他们的时候发现
but they're still the same nasty half
但他们仍然是同一个讨厌的一半
here half their problem of packages
这里有一半的包裹问题
split across multiple jars in fact if
实际上，如果多个罐子分开
you think about it the class path is
你想想，上课的路径是
crazy with a hundred and ten jars there
那里一百一百个罐子疯狂
are over 12,000 possible interactions
超过12,000种可能的互动
between classes in different jars
在不同罐子中的类之间
each one starting a linear search the
每个开始线性搜索
classpath is the ultimate in AirAsia
classpath是亚航的终极选择
whatever you know about the structure of
无论你知道什么结构
your application the classpath throws it
您的应用程序的类路径将其抛出
away and connect every jar to every
离开并连接每个罐子到每个
other jar with modules a module info
其他带有模块的jar模块信息
Java you're telling resolution what you
Java，您要告诉解决方案
know about the structure of your
了解你的结构
application and it uses that information
应用程序并使用该信息
to provide safety and performance at
提供安全性和性能
both compile-time and run-time now with
现在无论是编译时还是运行时
all of this talk of dependencies and
所有关于依赖的讨论和
resolution and the module path I know
分辨率和我知道的模块路径
what you're thinking where are the
你在想什么
version numbers who is thinking where
谁在想哪里的版本号
are the version numbers yes a number of
是版本号吗
people are think you where the version
人们都认为你在哪里版本
numbers can my module and the world
数字可以使我的模块和世界
require x and y where x requires version
需要x和y，其中x需要版本
1 of some library and y requires version
某些库中有1个，而y需要版本
2 of the same library now this is a
现在是同一个图书馆的2
difficult problem the problem with
困难的问题
multiple versions is that a class loader
多个版本是一个类加载器
can't have two classes with the same
不能有两个同一个类
packaging class name now if you're using
现在使用包装类名称
maven it will and you have some version
会的，你有一些版本
dependencies it will pick one of the
依赖关系，它将选择其中之一
versions for you in which case you are
适用于您的版本
not getting the two versions you thought
没有得到您认为的两个版本
you were or in some cases depending on
您曾经或在某些情况下取决于
the artifact names it'll put them both
工件名称将它们都放入
on the class path in which case you get
在这种情况下，您会得到
the split package problem now you've
拆分包问题，现在您已经
been thinking it's possible with maven
一直在想Maven有可能
to have multiple versions because no one
有多个版本，因为没有人
stopped you from doing it but in reality
阻止了您这样做，但实际上
you cannot do it without playing games
你不玩游戏就做不到
with class loaders which maven doesn't
与类加载器，Maven没有
do now if you do play the game where
如果您在哪里玩游戏，现在就做
every module is loaded in its own class
每个模块都在自己的类中加载
loader you would better make sure the
装载机，您最好确保
objects from version 1 and version 2 of
版本1和版本2的对象
the library don't leak out to a common
图书馆不要泄漏给普通人
caller like hello worlds otherwise
呼叫者像你好世界否则
you'll get the dreaded class cast
你会得到可怕的课堂演员
exception where you can't cast foo to
无法将foo强制转换为的异常
foo because the foo from library 1 and
foo，因为来自库1和的foo
the food from library 2 are different
库2的食物不同
ok you're thinking this is this seems
好的，您在想，这似乎是
the complicated problem and class
复杂的问题和阶级
loaders are complicated nevermind
装载机很复杂，没关系
multiple versions of a library forget
一个库的多个版本忘记了
that can I just say that by module one's
我可以这样说
version 2 of some library and not that
一些库的第2版，而不是
buggy version 1 well now you're the why
越野车版本1很好，现在您就是为什么
on the slide you want version 2 you're
在您想要版本2的幻灯片上
sure of it
确定
but you might be your module might be
但是你可能是你的模块可能是
reused in a larger application where
在更大的应用程序中重复使用
someone else is equally sure they want
别人同样确定他们想要
version one so the module system forces
版本一，因此模块系统强制
you to pick a single version of each
您为每个选择一个版本
module required by the application in
应用程序所需的模块
module in photo Java you require a
Photo Java中的模块，您需要
module by name not by name in version
模块名称而不是版本名称
when the compiler or runtime scans the
当编译器或运行时扫描
system image or the module path looking
系统映像或模块路径查找
for that named module only the first
对于该命名模块，只有第一个
module of that name is found so just
找到那个名字的模块，所以
like it's up to the tooling to help you
就像是由工具来帮助您
associate packages with a module it's up
将软件包与模块关联起来
to the tooling also to help you pick
工具也可以帮助您选择
that single version of your dependencies
依赖的那个单一版本
so there's a little more to say about
所以还有更多要说的
that a lot later if I have time but the
如果我有时间，那会很多，但是
thing to remember for now is that a
现在要记住的是
module is a set of packages designed for
模块是一组用于
reuse they offer strong encapsulation
重用它们提供强大的封装
and reliable dependencies and module
可靠的依赖关系和模块
aware tooling will be a big part of the
意识到工具将是
modular development experience moving
模块化的开发经验感动
swiftly on let's talk about how we would
快点让我们谈谈如何
take an existing application and migrate
使用现有的应用程序并迁移
it to modules now since it's impossible
现在将其添加到模块中，因为这是不可能的
to modularize the Java ecosystem all at
将Java生态系统全部模块化
once we're going to be living with a
一旦我们将与一个
combination of modular code that's
模块化代码的组合
modular jars on the module path and non
模块路径上的模块化jar和非
modular code that traditional jars I
传统的罐子我的模块化代码
don't wanna call them I don't want to
不想打电话给他们，我不想
call them legacy jars they're just jars
称它们为旧罐子，它们只是罐子
on the classpath for a while that's fine
在类路径上一段时间可以
and JDK 9 has tools for easing the
而JDK 9提供了一些工具来简化
migration that's what this section is
这就是本节的迁移
about so we'll start with a simple
关于，所以我们将从一个简单的开始
application that we want to migrate from
我们要从中迁移的应用程序
the class path at heart it has three
核心的课堂路径有三个
layers at the top of your application
应用程序顶部的图层
jars might be more than one of these
罐子可能不止一个
because you've got so many packages
因为你有很多包
right at the bottom is the JDK and in
底部是JDK，
the middle there's a bunch of library
中间有一堆图书馆
jars downloaded from the internet and
从互联网下载的罐子和
thrown on the class path now I've hinted
现在我暗示了在类路径上抛出
that we've turned the JDK into modules
我们已经将JDK变成了模块
and in this section green boxes will
在此部分，绿色框将
represent
代表
modules you've already seen Java base
您已经看过Java基础的模块
and you won't be surprised to learn
而且您不会惊讶于学习
there are also modules for logging
还有用于记录的模块
database access XML processing Java
数据库访问XML处理Java
logging Java sequel Java XML and many
记录Java续集Java XML和许多
more
更多
but our application isn't modularized
但是我们的应用程序没有模块化
and nor any of the libraries should we
而且我们也不应该使用任何图书馆
monitor eyes the application it's up to
监控应用程序的状态
you you can just run it on the class
你可以在课堂上运行它
path like you always did
像往常一样的道路
class path is not going away in jeddah
吉达上课的路不会消失
k9 but we modularized the jdk for a
k9，但我们将jdk模块化
reason to improve security through
通过以下方式提高安全性的理由
strong encapsulation and stability
强大的封装性和稳定性
through reliable dependences
通过可靠的依赖
applications might want to benefit from
应用程序可能想从中受益
this just like the jdk does there's
就像jdk那样
nothing special about the jdk modules so
jdk模块没什么特别的
just modules so let's see how we might
只是模块，所以让我们看看如何
turn this application into modules let's
将此应用程序转换为模块
imagine the application is in two jars
想象应用程序在两个罐子里
main code in my app jar helper code in
我的应用程序jar帮助程序代码中的主要代码
my lib jar and let's also imagine that
我的lib jar，让我们也想像一下
the soup of library jars is limited to
图书馆罐子的汤仅限于
jackson the JSON processing library
杰克逊JSON处理库
jackson comes as three jars core data
杰克逊作为三个罐子的核心数据而来
bind and annotations and we have the
绑定和注释，我们有
modular jdk on the bottom this is how
底部的模块化JDK这是如何
we'd run the application today we've got
我们今天要运行应用程序
to set up the Lib directory to include
设置Lib目录以包括
our application jars and our library
我们的应用程序jar和我们的库
jars pointing the class path out of them
罐子指出了他们的课堂道路
then run the application using the java
然后使用Java运行应用程序
launcher one of the things we'd gain by
发射器之一，我们将获得的东西
modularizing is not having to list out
模块化不必列出
the dependencies on the command-line in
命令行中的依赖项
script and where they can typos no one
脚本，他们可以在其中输入错误
will detect anything's wrong until much
直到发现很多错误
later so let's look at a scenario for
稍后，让我们来看一个场景
migrating this application top down here
从上向下迁移此应用程序
we first modularize the application jars
我们首先将应用程序jar模块化
without modularizing
没有模块化
the library jars now in general if you
现在，如果您在图书馆里
depend on third-party libraries you're
取决于您使用的第三方库
depending on them to modularize and we
依靠它们进行模块化，我们
can make it easier for libraries to
可以使图书馆更容易
modularize but generally we all have to
模块化，但是通常我们都必须
wait for them to do it no one can force
等待他们做，没有人可以强迫
them so it may well be that some of the
他们，所以很可能是一些
libraries you depend on are not
您所依赖的库不是
modularized yet that's okay now for your
模块化，但现在可以了
application jars that you do control the
您可以控制应用程序的jar
obvious path is to turn them one-to-one
显而易见的途径是将它们一对一
into modular jars
放入模块化的罐子里
where each jar has a module in photo
每个罐子在照片中都有一个模块
class file this is not always possible
类文件并不总是可能的
especially if the code in the jars has
特别是如果罐子中的代码具有
cyclic dependencies but let's go with it
循环依赖，但让我们一起去吧
for now now if we're going to turn each
现在，如果我们要把每个
application jar into a modular jar we'll
将应用程序jar放入模块化jar中
need to write a module declaration in
需要在其中编写模块声明
module in photo Java that gives a name a
照片Java中的模块，名称为
list of required modules and a list of
所需模块列表和
exported packages the names are easy my
导出的软件包的名称很容易
after my Lib we don't yet know though
我的解放后，我们还不知道
what each module depends on we can make
每个模块取决于我们可以做什么
manual analysis of the source files of
手动分析源文件
the class files but there's an easier
类文件，但是更容易
way the Jade EPS tool Jade EPS
Jade EPS工具的方式Jade EPS
scans class files or jar files and tells
扫描类文件或jar文件并告诉
you what code from other jar files that
您从其他jar文件中获得了哪些代码
code depends on now Jade EPS actually
代码实际上取决于现在的Jade EPS
came with JDK 8 and there's an improved
JDK 8附带了一个改进的功能
version in JDK 9 now while this isn't a
现在不是JDK 9中的版本
perfect solution come on to that it's a
完美的解决方案来了，这是一个
pretty good start so we'll run Jade Epps
很好的开始，所以我们将运行Jade Epps
on the application jars the Jackson
在应用程序上的罐子杰克逊
libraries are assumes to be on the class
假设图书馆在课堂上
path here and we see that my app jar
路径在这里，我们看到我的应用程序罐
depends on two of the Jackson jars which
取决于两个杰克逊罐子
remember and not modularized yet this is
记住并且没有模块化，但这是
just looking at the the references in
只是看参考
bytecode and of course on my little jar
字节码，当然还有我的小罐子
plus my app jar depends on the JDK
再加上我的app jar取决于JDK
modules Java base and Java sequel say my
Java基础模块和Java续集说我的
live jar only depends on Java base so
实时jar仅取决于Java基础，因此
that's nice and simple now we can write
很好，很简单，现在我们可以写
our module declarations let's start with
我们的模块声明让我们开始
the easy one the helper code in my lib
我库中的简单助手代码
we know it depends on Java base we can
我们知道这取决于Java基础
write requires Java base though I've
虽然我已经写了需要Java基础
sort of been stringing you along you
一直在串扰你
don't have to it's always put in for you
不必总是为您放置
by the compiler because every Java
由编译器，因为每个Java
program ultimately relies on java.lang
程序最终依赖于java.lang
objects so you always what you cannot
对象，所以您总是无法做到
not require Java base and from the Jade
不需要Java基础和Jade
EPS run we we knew that my app jar
EPS运行，我们知道我的应用程序罐
depends on my lip if we'd run Jade Epps
如果我们跑翡翠，取决于我的嘴唇
with more options we'd have seen that in
更多的选择，我们会看到
particular my app jar needs a particular
特别是我的应用程式罐子需要特别
package in my Lib now we could write
打包在我的Lib中，现在我们可以写
exports a package in this module
在此模块中导出软件包
declaration to allow anyone
声明允许任何人
access the package but if we're sure
访问软件包，但是如果我们确定的话
that no one except my app will need
除了我的应用程序之外，没有人需要
access we can use a qualified export to
访问我们可以使用合格的出口
maximize the encapsulation to say that
最大化封装来说明
package there is exported only to code
那里的包只导出到代码
in my app let's turn to the module
在我的应用程序中，让我们转到模块
declaration for my app it requires my
为我的应用程序声明它需要我的
lib no surprise and some JDK modules and
lib并不奇怪，还有一些JDK模块和
we know it's going to use Jackson but
我们知道它将使用杰克逊，但
we're not sure yet how to write the
我们还不确定如何编写
requires directives because they're not
需要指令，因为它们不是
modules yet does that mean that we which
模块，但这并不意味着我们
means you have to turn Jackson into
意味着你必须把杰克逊变成
modules before you can write this
模块，然后才能写这篇
declaration that would be unfortunate
不幸的宣言
since we you don't control the Jackson
因为我们你不控制杰克逊
jar files if only there was some way for
如果只有某种方式可以保存jar文件
the Jackson jar files to somehow become
杰克逊的jar文件以某种方式成为
modules automatically look how green
模块自动看起来绿色
they're going we don't know we didn't
他们要走了，我们不知道我们没有
write Jackson we don't know what their
写杰克逊，我们不知道他们是什么
dependencies and exports would be but we
依赖和出口将是但我们
have a pretty good idea of what the
对什么有一个很好的主意
names would be they basically be the
名称将基本上是
same names as the jars if we could do
如果可以的话，与罐子的名字相同
that we could finish writing the module
我们可以完成模块的编写
declaration for my app happy faces on
我的应用声明幸福的表情
those requires directives we'd have a
这些需要指令，我们会有一个
lovely module graph with my app
我的应用程序的可爱模块图
depending on my lib and Jackson Koren
取决于我的lib和杰克逊·科伦
Jackson data bind and Java base and Java
杰克逊数据绑定和Java基础和Java
sequel and my Lib depending on Java base
续集和我的Lib取决于Java基础
the good news is we can do this
好消息是我们可以做到这一点
with automatic modules an automatic
带有自动模块
module is a module whose declaration is
module是其声明为
inferred by the module system from a
由模块系统从
traditional jar that you have placed on
您放在的传统广口瓶
the convert module path they're real
它们是真实的转换模块路径
modules there they're really there at
模块在那里，他们真的在那里
runtime you don't change the jar file I
运行时，您不需要更改jar文件
can get this across enough you don't
可以让您获得足够的收益
change the jar file in any way because
以任何方式更改jar文件，因为
you don't know anything about what it's
你对它一无所知
doing the module name of an automatic
做一个自动的模块名称
module that you require is derived from
您需要的模块派生自
the jar file name it exports all this
jar文件名，它导出所有这一切
packages and it requires all other
包，它需要所有其他
modules in effect automatic modules mean
有效模块是指自动模块
that today's jars are already tomorrow
今天的罐子已经是明天了
modules now once automatic modules
模块现在是一次自动模块
spring into existence for Jackson core
杰克逊核心的存在
Jackson data binds and Jackson
杰克逊数据绑定和杰克逊
annotation because you move you put
注解，因为您移动了
those jars on the module path the module
模块上的那些jar路径
graph looks quite different because the
图看起来很不一样，因为
automatic modules basically say requires
自动模块基本上说要求
everything they require each other they
他们彼此需要的一切
require all the modules in the JDK image
需要JDK映像中的所有模块
and they require all of your modules as
他们需要您所有的模块
well and they explore all their packages
好，他们探索了他们所有的包裹
now this might not be the set of
现在这可能不是
requires and exports that the Jackson
要求并出口杰克逊
maintainer x' would write by hands um
维护者x'会用手写um
but it's actually the way automatic
但这实际上是自动方式
modules do this is a feature not a bug
模块这样做是功能而非错误
because it emulates the behavior of the
因为它模仿了
classpath it provides the maximum
它提供了最大的类路径
possible compatibility surface for code
可能的代码兼容性表面
in jar files and it's actually better
在jar文件中，实际上更好
than when everything was a jar on the
比起一切都在罐子上
classpath for example you have to look
例如，您必须查看类路径
carefully there is no arrow from my lib
小心地，我的库里没有箭
to my app so there's no danger of helper
到我的应用程序，因此没有助手的危险
code in my Lib accidentally reaching
Lib中的代码意外到达
into my apps internals on the classpath
进入我在类路径中的应用程序内部
code in my live jar could access code in
我的实时jar中的代码可以访问以下代码
my app dot jar my lip dot jar could
我的应用程式点罐我的嘴唇点罐
access code in my aperture quite easily
轻松访问我的光圈中的代码
without really even knowing it and that
甚至根本不知道
causes maintenance headaches down the
导致维护头痛
road now you might think we could do
现在你可能认为我们可以做到
better
更好
perhaps the module system could run Jade
也许模块系统可以运行Jade
EPS on the Jackson jars at startup and
杰克逊罐子在启动时的EPS
try to figure out what modules the Jax
尝试找出Jax的哪些模块
and jars require unfortunately this
和罐子需要这个
wouldn't really help the reason is that
真的没有帮助，原因是
libraries like Jackson often make use of
像杰克逊这样的图书馆经常利用
core reflection the java.lang reflect
核心反射java.lang反射
API to inspect application classes
用于检查应用程序类的API
dynamically Jade EPS can see the use of
可以动态看到Jade EPS的使用
core reflection but it can't predict
核心反射，但无法预测
statically what classes will be
静态将是什么类
inspected dynamically and in fact the
动态检查，实际上
Jackson Beta bind module does exactly
Jackson Beta绑定模块的功能完全一样
this kind of reflection it's going to
这种思考将
grow all over your application classes
在您的所有应用程序类中扩展
so it can convert between them and JSON
这样它就可以在它们和JSON之间转换
documents so if my app has classes for
文档，如果我的应用程序具有
which it wants Jax and data binding we
它想要Jax和数据绑定
want the effect of saying that Jax and
想要说Jax和
data bind requires my app amongst many
数据绑定需要我的应用程序众多
other things
其他事情
that's exactly what automatic modules
这正是自动模块
give you is one more wrinkle when code
给你代码时的另一皱纹
that was that was Jackson going up to my
那是杰克逊走向我的
app when code in my app calls the
应用程式中的程式码呼叫
Jackson API it passes its own class
Jackson API通过自己的类
object there it is the far right the
那里的对象是最右边的
intent is that Jackson data bind can
目的是Jackson数据绑定可以
create an instance of that application
创建该应用程序的实例
class my value and then reflectively set
分类我的价值，然后反思地设定
the name and age fields of this my value
此值的名称和年龄字段
instance based on the content of this
基于此内容的实例
here JSON document however this code
这里是JSON文档，但是此代码
fails because we never got around to
之所以失败，是因为我们从来没有到过
saying what my app exports to Jackson
说我的应用程序输出到Jackson的内容
data binds now this in some sense is is
现在数据绑定在某种意义上是
gentle because my app doesn't really
温柔，因为我的应用程序不是真的
have an API it's an application but if
有一个API，它是一个应用程序，但是如果
it wants to allow Jackson to manipulate
它想让杰克逊操纵
instances of its classes by reflection
通过反射查看其类的实例
then my app still need to export some
那么我的应用仍然需要导出一些
packages strong encapsulation applies
适用于强封装的软件包
not only to references from one module
不仅是来自一个模块的参考
turn to another compile time but also
转向另一个编译时间
for reflective access at runtime if a
用于在运行时进行反射访问
module doesn't export a package then
然后模块不导出包
code in other modules can't inspect the
其他模块中的代码无法检查
classes by reflection now a reflective
通过反射的类现在是反射的
relationship between application code
应用程序代码之间的关系
and library code is common application
和库代码是常见的应用
containers might walk over classes to
容器可能会遍历类
find annotated methods to be exposed as
找到要公开的注释方法
endpoints dependency injection
端点依赖注入
frameworks will call your methods
框架将调用您的方法
reflectively serialization frameworks
反思性序列化框架
will reflectively create and modify
将反思地创建和修改
instances of your classes many
您的课程实例很多
applications use these facilities and in
应用程序使用这些功能
order for them to work we somehow have
为了他们工作，我们不知何故
to expose otherwise encapsulated
暴露否则封装
application classes via reflection now
现在通过反射的应用程序类
we could do that by exporting the
我们可以通过导出
application packages but there's a
应用程序包，但有一个
finer-grained mechanism that is specific
具体的细粒度机制
to access by reflection that mechanism
通过反射访问该机制
is the open
是开放的
directive so let's say our domain
指令，所以我们说我们的域名
classes like my value are in this comm
像我的价值观这样的课程在这个通讯中
my app domain package we can open that
我的应用程序域包中，我们可以打开它
package up for access by reflection to
打包以通过反射访问
all modules or we can qualify the opens
所有模块，否则我们可以限定空缺
just like we did for exports before
就像我们以前做出口一样
opening a package is narrower and deeper
打开包装更窄更深
than exporting a package narrower
比出口包裹要窄
because opens only has an effect at
因为打开只会在
runtime
运行
whereas exports applies at compile-time
而出口在编译时适用
and run-time but deeper because opens
和运行时，但更深入，因为开放
allows all elements of that package to
允许该包的所有元素
be accessed by reflection
通过反射访问
whereas exports only allows reflective
而出口只允许反射
access to public elements it sort of a
访问公共元素
lot simpler to use than to explain in
使用起来比解释起来简单得多
some ways we could go in the other
我们可以采取其他一些方式
direction to rather than opening a
而不是打开一个方向
specific package for reflection we could
可以反思的特定包装
open all of our my app packages for
打开我们的所有我的应用程序包
reflection by anyone you declare you
您宣布自己的任何人的反思
could declare my app as an open module
可以将我的应用声明为开放模块
open modules give you half the benefits
开放式模块为您带来一半的好处
of modularity you get reliable
模块化，您将获得可靠
dependencies all the requires clauses
依赖所有require子句
will get resolved at compile-time and
将在编译时解决，并且
run-time but not strong encapsulation
运行时，但封装不强
because anyone can reflect their way
因为任何人都可以反映自己的方式
into the private fields and methods of
进入私人领域和方法
my app but since frameworks that reflect
我的应用程序，但由于框架反映了
deeply into application code are a
深入应用程序代码是
reality in everyday Java development
日常Java开发中的现实
application code can't always be
应用程序代码不能总是
strongly encapsulated and open modules
高度封装和开放的模块
we think are a pragmatic solution it's
我们认为这是一个务实的解决方案
up to the application a developer to
取决于应用程序的开发者
choose note that this open module
选择注意，此打开模块
doesn't but an open module can still use
不会，但是打开的模块仍可以使用
exports directives in module inferred
推断模块中的导出指令
Java to define and of a static API for
Java定义和静态API
use at compile time and now we can run
在编译时使用，现在我们可以运行
our modular application with a simple
我们的模块化应用程序
invocation assume our modular jars
调用假定我们的模块化罐子
that's my app jar and my libs are and
那是我的应用程序罐，我的库是和
now in EM lip and the unchanged Jaxon
现在处于EM lip和未更改的Jaxon中
jars are still in Lib we just have to
罐子仍在库中，我们只需要
tell the Java launcher where the module
告诉Java启动器模块在哪里
pass should be set and it will figure
应该设置通行证，它将计算
out which of the jars on the module path
找出模块路径中的哪个jar
should be turned into automatic modules
应该变成自动模块
so when you migrate each application jar
因此，当您迁移每个应用程序jar时
is usually a good candidate to be a
通常是一个很好的候选人
module each library jar will migrate at
每个库jar的模块迁移
its own pace and automatic modules mean
自己的节奏和自动模块意味着
you are not waiting for the weakest link
您不是在等待最薄弱的环节
that would be very sad we had to do that
那很可悲，我们必须这样做
nearly there let's talk about the
几乎在那里，我们来谈谈
the JDK roughly speaking the size of the
JDK大致来说
Java platform has been going up with the
Java平台已经跟上了
square of the major version number Java
主要版本号Java的平方
1.0 had only a few hundred classes Java
1.0只有几百个Java类
9 is tens of thousands the JDK 1.0
9是数以万计的JDK 1.0
download it it still installs and no 7
下载它仍然安装并且没有7
was under 4 Meg the JDK 9 download is a
在4 Meg以下时，JDK 9下载是一个
hundred and 50 Meg
一百五十兆
now when the Java platform was small the
现在，当Java平台很小时，
organization of the JDK code wasn't a
JDK代码的组织不是一个
problem but every year the platform grew
问题，但平台每年都在增长
a little bigger and now it's huge and
更大一点，现在又很大了
monolithic in reality the Java platform
实际上是Java平台的整体式
is not one thing it's more like 25
不是一回事，更像是25
separate frameworks including the swing
单独的框架，包括秋千
UI framework the crypto framework
UI框架crypto框架
scripting framework multiple xml
脚本框架多XML
processing frameworks and so on there's
处理框架等等
no reason these separate frameworks have
这些单独的框架没有理由
to be so tightly coupled in one download
在一次下载中紧密结合
in fact it's an impediment for us in
实际上，这对我们来说是一个障碍
developing the JDK the overly tight
开发过紧的JDK
coupling raises development and testing
耦合提高了开发和测试
costs which turns into slower platform
成本使平台变慢
evolution plus the larger the surface of
演化加上更大的表面
your platform more difficult it is to
您的平台更困难
secure and it's an impediment to lots of
安全，这是很多障碍
users both those who want to run their
用户都想要运行他们的
applications on smaller devices and
较小设备上的应用程序以及
those who want to run more instances of
那些想要运行更多实例的
their application on large systems even
它们在大型系统上的应用
if you only want a part of the JDK
如果您只想要JDK的一部分
you've got to take all of it
你必须全部拿走
the good news of course is that JDK 9 is
好消息当然是JDK 9是
modular we've taken the monolithic RT
模块化，我们采用了单片RT
jar file and broken it up into a few
jar文件并将其分解为几个
dozen modules some of these are part of
十几个模块，其中一些是其中的一部分
the Java SE specification some are just
Java SE规范只是
just parts of the jdk implementation
只是JDK实现的一部分
here's a graph of the Java SE modules we
这是我们的Java SE模块的图形
can see at the bottom there's Java base
可以看到底部有Java基础
which everything depends on and which
一切都取决于哪个
depends on nothing itself we've broken
依靠什么本身我们都没有打破
out the various frameworks into their
将各种框架
own modules instrumentation logging XML
自己的模块检测日志记录XML
scripting
脚本编写
etc which you can use by requires or not
您可以根据需要使用等
as your needs dictate at the top there's
根据您的需求在顶部
a Java SE module which has no actual
没有实际的Java SE模块
code in it but just has dependencies so
其中的代码，但只有依赖关系
you can say requires Java SE and be
您可以说需要Java SE并且
guaranteed to have all of these modules
保证拥有所有这些模块
available it's worth mentioning that
值得一提的是
merely finding these module boundaries
仅找到这些模块边界
which might be obvious in hindsight will
在事后看来这可能是显而易见的
they tremendous engineering efforts
他们付出了巨大的工程努力
decoupling a monolith is much harder
解耦整体要困难得多
than building a decoupled system from
比建立一个解耦的系统
the beginning we had to undo years of
我们不得不撤消多年的开始
bad assumptions and accidental couplings
错误的假设和偶然的耦合
inside our tea jar but going forward the
在我们的茶缸里，但是向前
discipline imposed by the module system
模块系统施加的纪律
will prevent us from accidentally
可以防止我们意外
sliding back into a big ball of mud I
滑回一个大泥球我
mean a monolith the difference between
意味着整体之间的区别
solid lines and dotted lines is an
实线和虚线是
excellent question we should discuss
我们应该讨论的好问题
later the Java SE modules are actually a
后来的Java SE模块实际上是
small subset of the modules you'll find
您会发现模块的一小部分
in the JDK 9 system image if you do Java
如果您使用Java，则在JDK 9系统映像中
- - list modules you'll see those two
--列出模块，您将看到这两个模块
dozen or so in Java SE modules Java
Java SE模块中的十几个Java
based sequel logging etc as well as some
基于续集测井等，以及一些
Java FX modules and then a large number
Java FX模块，然后大量
of JDK specific modules JDK compiler JDK
JDK特定模块的说明JDK编译器JDK
Java doc dedicate J shell jdk Jade EPS
Java文档专用J Shell JDK Jade EPS
is its own module the Jade EPS tool is a
是自己的模块，Jade EPS工具是
column in the middle and so on and so on
列在中间，依此类推
they're all located in the system image
它们都位于系统映像中
but apart from that they're just
但除此之外，他们只是
ordinary modules with requires and
带有require和的普通模块
exports directives like any other I'd
出口指令就像我想要的其他任何指令一样
like to spend some time by which I mean
我喜欢花一些时间
the remaining time on expectations of
期望的剩余时间
compatibility from JDK 9 this applies to
适用于JDK 9的兼容性
everyone here and it doesn't because
每个人都在这里，这不是因为
you're not the ones who necessarily
你不是那些一定
relying on some of this stuff but it's
依靠其中一些东西，但是
worth everyone understanding what's
值得每个人了解什么
going on here some misc base64 encode
在这里进行一些其他base64编码
and some misc base64 decoder does anyone
和一些其他的base64解码器可以执行任何操作
use them
使用它们
oh that was more how I was expecting no
哦，这更是我所期待的
hands I was going to say are but all of
我要说的手不过是
your libraries do but okay so those
您的图书馆确实可以，但是那些
classes are gone in JDK 9 they are not
JDK 9中没有类，但不是
strongly encapsulated they're physically
高度封装，它们在物理上
not there so this met this might break
不在那里，所以遇到这个可能会破坏
some libraries that you use if it does
您使用的某些库
file a bug with the library maintainer
向库维护者提交错误
z' and tell them to use the excellent
并告诉他们使用优秀的
base64 class introduced in JDK 8 second
JDK中引入的base64类8秒
who uses some miss gun safe same hands
谁用一些安全的小姐枪
are different hands okay so some mystic
是不同的手好吗，所以有些神秘
on safe has not gone away the Sun misc
安全未消失太阳杂项
package is exported by a JDK module to
包由JDK模块导出到
the hand supported and the unsafe class
手扶和不安全等级
is still there however while the Sun
还在，但是当太阳
misc package is exported many JDK
misc包导出了许多JDK
internal packages are not and again this
内部软件包不是一次又一次
might break some libraries that you use
可能会破坏您使用的某些库
because library code will fail if it
因为如果库代码失败
tries to access classes in the concealed
尝试访问隐藏的类
package common crypto Sun provider or
打包通用的加密Sun提供商或
comma Sun or the patch is X YZ internal
逗号Sun或补丁是X YZ内部
Jax P or Sun nioh CH or Sun net www or
Jax P或Sun nioh CH或Sun net www或
Sun reflect annotation or some security
Sun反映注释或某些安全性
x.509 and most of you don't care about
x.509，你们大多数人都不在乎
any of these packages but the person who
这些软件包中的任何一个，但
does has a problem finally we need to
确实有问题，最后我们需要
talk again about exports exporting a
再谈出口出口
package means you can compile and run
软件包意味着您可以编译和运行
against the public members of the public
反对公众
classes of that package it's an API
该包的类是一个API
exporting a package either from a Java
从Java导出软件包
mounted JDK module or from your module
安装的JDK模块或从您的模块
is not about letting library code use
不是要让库代码使用
reflection to access private elements if
反射访问私有元素，如果
you recall that was what an open module
你还记得那是一个开放的模块
allowed but none of the JDK modules are
允许，但没有JDK模块
open let me give you an example the Java
打开让我给你举个Java的例子
based module exports a package called
基于模块的模块会导出一个名为
Java dot security which contains a
Java点安全性包含
public class called key store the
称为密钥库的公共类
purpose of this class when I find my
当我找到自己的班级时
pointer
指针
the purpose of this class is and I quote
这个课程的目的是
a storage facility for cryptographic
密码存储设备
keys and certificates if ever there was
密钥和证书（如果有）
a public class in an API whose private
API中的公共类，其私有
fields should be strongly encapsulated
字段应严格封装
it's this one well here is a stack
这是一口井，这里是一堆
overflow question from July 2016 someone
从2016年7月开始有人溢出问题
this is on JDK 8 was using reflection to
这是在JDK 8上使用反射来
access a private field in the keystore
访问密钥库中的私有字段
class and not only did this person feel
上课，不仅这个人感到
free to reflect over key stores
免费反映主要商店
internals they actually got annoyed when
他们实际上在什么时候惹恼了内部人员
the internals were changed in a JDK
内部结构在JDK中已更改
update a JDK 8 updates the Java security
更新JDK 8更新Java安全性
package in JDK 9 is exported so you can
JDK 9中的软件包已导出，因此您可以
code against the keystore api not so
针对密钥库api的代码并非如此
that you can reflect over key stores
您可以反映在关键商店
internals one of the reasons we think
内部因素是我们认为的原因之一
strong encapsulation is so important is
强大的封装是如此重要
that it will let us evolve the JDK more
它将使我们进一步发展JDK
rapidly and reliably because we all know
快速可靠，因为我们都知道
that no one can rely on unspecified
没有人可以依靠未指定的
implementation details unfortunately of
不幸的是实施细节
course there's there's this this guy's
当然有这个人的
basically writing a library there's
基本上写一个图书馆
library code out there which has been
库代码在那里
relying on these details for years so
多年来一直依靠这些细节
there's going to be some migration pain
会有一些迁移的痛苦
for these libraries and for the
这些库和
applications that rely on these
依赖这些的应用程序
libraries if this happens to your hap
图书馆，如果这发生在你的hap
Legation then again please file a bug
领事再请提交一个错误
with the library maintenance finally
终于有了图书馆维修
finally I again just want to make you
最后我再次想让你
aware that some internal aspects of the
意识到
JDK have been overhauled and again it
对JDK进行了大修，然后再次进行
probably won't affect you but it might
可能不会影响您，但可能
affect the libraries and tools you rely
影响您依赖的库和工具
on code that assumes there's a file
在假定有文件的代码上
called RTO Jarl tools jar in a
在一个叫做RTO Jarl的工具罐中
particular directory will fail on JDK 9
特定目录在JDK 9上将失败
scripts that try to patch the JDK with -
尝试使用以下命令修补JDK的脚本：
X blue class path slash P will fail on
X蓝色类路径斜线P将失败
JDK 9 code that assumes the application
假定应用程序的JDK 9代码
class loader is a URL class loader will
类加载器是一个URL类加载器
fail on JDK 9 code that assumes all JDK
在假定所有JDK的JDK 9代码上失败
classes are defined by the
类由
strap loader will fail on JDK 9 code
带加载程序将在JDK 9代码上失败
that assumes the version strings
假设版本字符串
reported by system properties begin with
系统属性报告的开头是
one dots will fail on JDK 9 again if you
如果您在JDK 9上再打一个点，
see libraries failing due to these
看到由于这些原因导致库失败
assumptions on never documented never
关于永不记录的假设
specified never standardized
指定从未标准化
implementation details file a bug with
实施细节文件中的错误
the library maintenance so the modular
库维护，因此模块化
JDK is modules all the way down some
JDK一直是一些模块
misc is exported JDK internal packages
misc导出了JDK内部软件包
are nots and beware of libraries relying
不是，要提防图书馆依赖
on JDK internals in JDK 9 a module is a
在JDK 9的JDK内部上，一个模块是
set of packages designed for reuse
一组旨在重用的软件包
automatic modules help migrates
自动模块有助于迁移
libraries and with modules the JDK can
库和模块，JDK可以
evolve more rapidly and reliably but
发展得更快，更可靠，但
popular libraries and tooling are not
流行的库和工具不是
yet all compatible with JDK 9 in the 2
但都与2中的JDK 9兼容
minutes remaining for the network the
网络剩余分钟数
last two slides and all of your
最后两张幻灯片和所有
questions are I need to acknowledge that
问题是我需要承认
there's a huge amount in the module
模块中有很多
system that I haven't had time to talk
我没时间说话的系统
about you can encapsulate resources in a
关于您可以将资源封装在
module largest classes you can express
您可以表达的模块最大类别
optional dependencies by programming
通过编程的可选依赖项
with services you can build custom
通过服务您可以自定义
system images with the j-link tool so
使用j-link工具制作系统映像
you can drop CORBA right now if you want
您可以立即删除CORBA
and you can in fact spin up multiple
实际上，您可以旋转多个
versions of a module with the layer API
带有层API的模块的版本
if you're interested in this kind of
如果您对此感兴趣
thing it recommends two books the first
它推荐两本书的第一本
is Java 9 modularity out now in early
Java 9模块化现在早已面世
access form it's a very pragmatic
访问表格，这是非常务实的
walkthrough of the entire module system
整个模块系统的演练
and the modular JDK the other book is
和模块化的JDK，另一本书是
java application architecture from 2012
2012年以来的Java应用程序架构
it's a principled look at constructing
这是构建的原则
modular applications it says I was
它说我是模块化应用程序
joined the title it's it's not specific
加入了标题，这不是特定的
to any module system really
真正适用于任何模块系统
it has a lot of very very good advice
它有很多非常非常好的建议
that applies whether you're using a
无论您使用的是
module system or just relying on
模块系统还是仅仅依靠
traditional jars about how to structure
关于如何构造的传统罐子
an application so the best thing you can
一个应用程序，所以你可以做到最好
do to prepare for jdk 9 is download an
为jdk 9做准备是下载
early access binary has anyone done that
抢先体验二进制文件有没有做过
some hands okay some hand thank you if
一些手好吗，如果谢谢你
you're a library maintainer these runge
您是这些维护人员的图书馆维护者
a depth to see what JDK internals you
深入了解您的JDK内部结构
rely on you can do this right now on JDK
依靠您现在就可以在JDK上执行此操作
8 that will that will work on JDK AIDS
8将对JDK AIDS起作用
everything you ever wanted to know about
您曾经想知道的一切
the module system is discussed on open
公开讨论模块系统
JDK in jet 261 I cannot emphasize enough
喷气飞机261中的JDK我无法强调
how much valuable information lives in
多少有价值的信息生活在其中
jet 261 there's also jet 260 which
射流261还有射流260
identifies the JDK internal classes like
标识JDK内部类，例如
some miss gun safe that are exposed in
一些暴露在其中的枪支小姐保险柜
JDK 9 jet 223 which defines the new
新定义的JDK 9 jet 223
version strings beginning 9 dots and jet
版本字符串开始于9点并喷射
220 which describes how RT jar has gone
220描述了RT jar的运行方式
away
远
finally jet 200 gives an overview of the
最后喷气200提供了一个概述
JDK modules but if you've already read
JDK模块，但如果您已经阅读过
jet 261 which should because it's very
喷射261，这应该是因为它非常
good there won't be any surprises and
好，不会有任何惊喜，
with that exactly the time thank you
正是那个时候，谢谢
very much so we now have negative time
非常多，所以我们现在有消极的时间
for questions so we all tealights you
提出问题，所以我们都欢迎您
someone had you had a question earlier
有人早些时候有一个问题
do this quickly
快做
versions of a jar in Jeddah k-8 on the
吉达k-8上的罐子版本
class path you would typically shade the
您通常会在
packages that that will continue to work
可以继续使用的软件包
jar files both on the class path and
jar文件在类路径和
modular jar files on the module path
模块路径上的模块化jar文件
there's nothing that thus better the
没有什么比这更好的了
specialness is all in the module info
特殊性全在模块信息中
dot class file the contents of those
点类文件的内容
module if they are in fact containing
模块，如果它们实际上包含
renamed rebased your word packages fine
重命名可以重新打包单词包
if your if you have if you have shaded
如果您有阴影的话
the package and renamed it even if it's
包并重命名，即使它是
being exported the there are different
出口有不同
they're different classes that was a
他们是不同的班级
question you had a question hey al how
问题，你有一个问题，嘿，怎么
do you test classes that are not
你测试不是
exported there are this is this is a
出口那里是这是一个
talk in itself the short answer is there
说话本身就是简短的答案
is a command line flag to patch classes
是修补类的命令行标志
into a module so you can access the
进入模块，以便您可以访问
internals GEB 261 has all the
内部部件GEB 261具有所有
information about that the real answer
关于真正答案的信息
is that testing frameworks that wish to
是希望的测试框架
test non-public non exported non open
测试非公开非出口非公开
elements of a module should use the
模块的元素应使用
method handles lookup API to access
方法处理要访问的查找API
module internals in a constrained way
模块内部约束
that is that is an entire days worth of
那就是一整天的价值
talk but you it only requires the
说话，但你只需要
testing framework to spin its
测试框架旋转
infrastructure once to use the write API
基础架构一次使用写API
I'm a question from the back yes
我是一个反面的问题，是的
was what the qualified export was let me
合格的出口才让我
go back that export exports the package
回到出口出口包装
to a specific friend module yes I think
到特定的朋友模块，是的，我认为
that is all we have time for again thank
这就是我们有时间再次感谢
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]